{
    "id": "d7b4bcb4590a4deeaad96fb7d6cec0db",
    "title": "Simple, Complex And Compound Sentence",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She didn’t realize that she was making a mistake.",
            "description": "Clauses connected by subordinating conjunctions or relative pronouns form complex sentences. ",
            "answers": [
                "complex",
                "simple",
                "compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "234512295bc3435c88c51a0453e4b425"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where have you been all this while?",
            "description": "A sentence that has just one finite verb is a simple sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "complex",
                "compound",
                "simple"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "76c748062bdc4c2789a57674edf5d879"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know the answer.",
            "description": "A sentence that has just one finite verb is a simple sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "complex",
                "simple",
                "compound"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d524aedc9ff645d9882537a879d1a7bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that she wanted to go.",
            "description": "Clauses connected by subordinating conjunctions or relative pronouns form complex sentences. ",
            "answers": [
                "simple",
                "complex",
                "compound"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3803e6b29cda48639b22f78a00379a0b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rahul is not only clever but also industrious.",
            "description": "Clauses connected by the conjunctions and, but, either...or, neither...nor, both...and form a compound sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "simple",
                "complex",
                "compound"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "479b9d06418d46b88c4cee3dd2316e86"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither this answer nor that answer is correct.",
            "description": "Clauses connected by the conjunctions and, but, either...or, neither...nor, both...and form a compound sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "compound",
                "simple",
                "complex"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7d6f4dd4fd96481792695c8dfcdcbca9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was angry because she had lied to him.",
            "description": "Clauses connected by subordinating conjunctions or relative pronouns form complex sentences. ",
            "answers": [
                "complex",
                "simple",
                "compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7f1e885e7b9f4e6bbae3ed0aeb0d4862"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will try until I succeed.",
            "description": "Clauses connected by subordinating conjunctions or relative pronouns form complex sentences. ",
            "answers": [
                "simple",
                "complex",
                "compound"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f4d9464a463a4cff88a4e34bf1af1751"
        },
        {
            "question": "Standing on tip-toe, he reached for the mango.",
            "description": "A sentence that has just one finite verb is a simple sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "compound",
                "simple",
                "complex"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c3b1680421d4e98a0e2da759d70461a"
        },
        {
            "question": "As they haven’t arrived yet, we will go without them.",
            "description": "Clauses connected by subordinating conjunctions or relative pronouns form complex sentences. ",
            "answers": [
                "simple",
                "compound",
                "complex"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "137082d4a6cf4ba1adbd60541d7b27a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is rich but he will not help anyone.",
            "description": "Clauses connected by the conjunctions and, but, either...or, neither...nor, both...and form a compound sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "complex",
                "simple",
                "compound"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f3e2eff6fdbe4082870d636c591172e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can wait or leave.",
            "description": "Clauses connected by the conjunctions and, but, either...or, neither...nor, both...and form a compound sentence. ",
            "answers": [
                "compound",
                "simple",
                "complex"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0dfafbfb6069404993981b9c3e4a0040"
        }
    ]
}